[ Dennis ] You better have
a good reason for getting us
out of bed this early, jerk.
I got a goddamn great reason
for getting you out of bed.
This bar is hemorrhaging money.
You gotta spend money
to make money.
Economics 101, dude.
You're bleeding us to death,
especially with that
company credit card you got.
That is for business expenses,
Frank. Everything on there
is a business expense.
Who spent $500
for laser hair removal?
Right over here, slick.
Don't wanna have
hair down there.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
Who spent $5,000
for a samurai sword?
Your head of security.
Yeah. Just wait till he saves
your life one day with it.
$6,000 on a camcorder.
Well, I've decided
what I'm gonna do...
is I'm going to take all those
hilarious characters...
that I've been creating
over the past several years--
I'm gonna put 'em on tape.
I'm gonna put 'em on YouTube.
That way I can get discovered by
a casting director or producer,
get some kind of
a TV development deal.
Yeah, right. So the point is,
Frank, is that these
are all business expenses.
See?
I mean, some are definitely
more realistic than others.
Yeah, not that one.
No, not at all.
But nonetheless, it was,
I believe, bought as
a business expense, so--
They're not business expenses.
What I bought
is a business expense.
What I bought is something
that's gonna save our asses.
Okay. Yeah. All right.
All right. What'd you get?
I bought a billboard.
Okay, so I'm thinking
we write on the billboard
in nice big letters,
"We have two for one
drink specials on Thursdays."
And on the bottom, you got
a hilarious picture of Greenman
kicking someone in the nuts.
And people go,
"Hey, what's this wacky place?
Where can I have those drinks?"
It is absolutely astonishing
how bad your ideas are.
How is that a bad idea?
Go sit down.
The adults are working.
Really?
Okay.
When we need a child,
we'll call you.
- Woo-hoo!
- Now, Dennis,
you and I on the same team--
hot chick up on the billboard,
sex sells, boom.
Oh, absolutely.
It's Advertising 101.
Long legs, taut breasts
and tight poopers.
I'm just gonna jump in here
real quick and point out...
that this is the point
in the conversation...
where I would volunteer
to be the girl on the billboard,
and then you guys would talk
about how ugly you think I am...
- and compare me
to some sort of giant bird.
- You look so much like a bird.
Dennis, I was
thinking fish recently.
Really?
Yeah. Her eyes are
so far apart, they're, like,
on the sides of her head.
Okay. Okay.
But I don't wanna be
on your billboard.
I'm not gonna ask to be
because you wouldn't
let me be on it anyway.
That's sensible
of you not to ask.
[ Mac ] God, no.
For the love of God,
there's no way you would be
up on that billboard.
- That is never gonna happen!
- Let me get the point out!
The point is--
Anything's better than you.
I don't wanna be
on your billboard,
and I'll tell you why.
I'm gonna take
one of my characters,
and I'm gonna launch
a viral video
and promote Paddy's myself.
A viral video?
There's about a billion
of those on YouTube.
- Who gives a shit, Dee?
- Oh, you think anybody gives
a shit about a billboard?
Uh, wake up, donkeys.
The Internet is where it's at,
and I'm going to be
an Internet sensation.
You know, you're totally right.
And if you don't mind,
I'm gonna come with you.
Maybe I can throw Greenman
into a couple of your videos,
you know, and work it out.
That'll get a lot
of hits, I think.
You can help me out, Charlie,
but we're not gonna put
Greenman into anything.
Well, we'll see about that.
We won't see about that.
Well, we will.
Mm-mmm.
All right.
Uh, later, dudes.
S.U. in your A's,
don't wear a "C"
and "J" all over your B's.
Why would he not wear a "C"?
I don't even know
what he's talking about
half the time, bro.
[ Mac ]
Hey, Frank.
Glad you're here, bro.
We're talkin' billboard ideas.
Yeah.
Don't waste your time.
I know what the billboard's
gonna look like already.
Two gorgeous girls up there,
giant cans,
me in the middle
with my thumbs up.
- Yeah!
- Well, that's just simply
not gonna happen.
Uh, actually,
maybe Frank has a point, dude.
Maybe we should
put a dude up there.
Certainly not him.
But if we put
some hot beefcake up there,
maybe it'll attract more chicks.
Yeah, that's a good point.
Okay, I like that.
You know what?
Let's slap my picture up there.
It's about time
I got my modeling career
off the ground anyway.
Don't flatter yourself.
You're not gonna
be up there...
because I am gonna be
the face of Paddy's Bar.
That's ridiculous, Frank.
You're, um,
ugly.
- What?
- Ugly.
- I'm ugly?
- Yeah.
With that anteater nose,
you're telling me I'm ugly?
My nose was chiseled
by the gods themselves,
Frank.
My body was sculpted
to the proportions
of Michelangelo's David.
You, on the other hand--
well, you're a pit of despair.
Frank, you disgust me.
You disgust everyone.
And you will never, ever,
be on that billboard.
[ Irish Accent ]
Good morning, Philadelphia.
I'm Crazy Paddy,
and I'm coming to you
from Paddy's Pub,
telling you to come on down,
where we're
slashing prices so low,
you won't need a pot of gold
to get sloppy.
So come on down to Paddy's.
It's insane!
What is that?
[ No Accent ]
Did you like that?
No. That's not what
YouTube videos are like.
Oh, that's a great character.
No, that's a bad commercial
you'd see on the
cable network or something.
Maybe you didn't get it.
I'm crazy 'cause I'm pricing
the beer too low.
Mmm, I think I got it.
The beer's too low for what
average beer prices should be.
You know what? Let's just do it
again. Maybe throw in some more
jokes or something. You know?
Make it a little funnier.
Make it funnier.
You're absolutely right.
You can make it funny.
You're a funny girl.
Good morning, Philadelphia.
I'm Crazy Pad--
[ Laughs ]
Oh!
Oh, my God.
Why?
Now that was funny!
Dee, that's awesome.
Why would you do that?
That's what
YouTube video is.
Are you insane?
You ever see the little girl
who's mashing the grapes...
and then slips
and she's, like--
Why would you do that, Charlie?
That's what
people wanna see!
Oh, my God!
People getting injured
or seriously hurt--
That's funny!
Okay?
Let's just do this.
This is--
Trust me. This is
what gets hits on YouTube.
All right. Are you ready?
Yeah. I was ready
from the--
Stop talking!
[ Sighs ]
I'm Crazy Paddy--
No. Okay.
Okay.
I'm Crazy Paddy--
[ Grunts ]
What are you doing?
You're flinching
every time now.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I can't concentrate
when I'm about to get
blasted in the face with a ball!
I'll blast you all over
if you flinch again.
Don't--
Let's just do this.
Action!
These--
[ Screams ]
Goddamn!
Oh! Yeah!
That was funny.
I don't like it, Charlie!
I don't think it's funny--
Yeah!
It's too much.
It just hurts too bad.
Bro, can you believe
how many hot chicks showed up...
for a casting call
for a billboard?
How have we not
done this before?
Yeah. Yeah, man.
Plus, think about it.
Dennis Reynolds,
40 feet tall and shirtless.
[ Door Opens ]
Oh! It's gonna be
so perfect.
Let's go. Just take
your places over there.
- Frank, what are you doing?
- We're lookin'
for models, right?
Yeah.
I went on a stud hunt.
I came back with beefcakes.
What are you talkin' about,
Frank? I'm the male model.
Uh, Rex. Rex.
Here you go.
What's Rex for?
We don't need Rex.
Take your shirt off.
Come on. You don't need
to take your shirt off.
- [ Whistles ]
- Okay. Well, if you're
looking for that.
- [ Cackles ]
Now that--
- That's what you want.
That is what
you call stallion.
[ Mac ] That is a stallion.
I didn't know you guys
were lookin' for a stallion.
I'm a stallion--
Ooh! Dennis.
Uh-- [ Groans ]
You think Frank's
got a point here?
I don't think he has a point.
I'm a stallion.
Uh--
[ Groaning ]
All right. This is messy.
Um, look, buddy.
2003 Dennis--
Okay, he was Grade "A"
prime beefcake.
No one is disputing that.
He was a stallion.
But 2008 Dennis is in decline.
Take a look at Rex here.
That is a body
that just won't quit.
I bet if you pop those pants
off, you're gonna find a bird
that just won't quit either,
and I think that'll
come in handy in this situation.
I think the problem here
is that your body quit.
Your bird quit.
And unfortunately,
it's no longer legit.
What the hell are you
talking about? My bird?
All right. Let's get back to--
to business here.
Attention, ladies! I'm gonna
need all the "A" cups to please
head for the back door.
[ Dee ]
Charlie, are you ready
with the camera?
Yeah.
I'm trying to set it up.
It takes a second, Dee.
Yeah.
All right. Who the hell is this
character that you're doing?
Oh, this one?
It's a really great one.
Her name's Martina Martinez,
and she is a streetwise
Puerto Rican girl...
- who's always quick
with a sassy comeback.
- Are you serious?
Yes. It's awesome. Let's
go over what we're doing again.
I go up. I talk.
You come in with the volleyball,
you hit him in the face
and you get out of there.
Okay. I'm gonna hit
a random person in the face
with a volleyball.
But don't come in too early,
'cause I got some material
I wanna do,
and I don't want you
to cut me off.
Because Saturday Night Live
is gonna really--
I think they're gonna love--
Do you really think that?
Charlie. Charlie.
Point it that way.
Go, go, go. Go.
[ Clears Throat ]
You know, I'm horrified
that he's here--
[ New York Accent ]
Um, excuse me.
Can I talk to youse?
What?
Youse a bunch
of white boys, right?
Can I ax you a question?
When you be in the clubs
and you be dancin',
why you look so stupid?
[ Laughs ]
I'm just playin'.
So, um, youse a big man, right,
but you got such tiny boots on.
That means you got
a small pecker. I'm sorry!
I'm just playin'.
I'm Martina Martinez.
[ Screaming ]
Oh!
Greenman!
Oh.
[ All Laughing ]
Okay, attention!
Ladies, gentlemen,
hotties and beefcakes.
You were brought here because
you are the most beautiful
people in all of Philadelphia,
and as such,
the honor has been bestowed
upon all of you...
to compete in Paddy's
First Next Top
Billboard Model contest.
- Uh, what's the pay?
- What?
- What is the pay?
- The pay, sir,
is getting your face
40 feet up on a billboard!
- So there's no pay then?
- I just told you
what the pay is.
He told you
what the goddamn pay was.
The billboard thing.
- Were you not listening?
- Well, I'm outta here.
Fine. Fine!
You leave!
You crybaby.
We don't need you people.
Everybody else!
Let's take their
lack of dedication
as a lesson, shall we?
Competitions like this
aren't about money.
They're about fame.
They are about putting yourself
on display to the world
and saying, "I'm good enough...
because I beat
everyone else."
That's right.
"And I got myself up
on a billboard."
Not so fast!
- The hell are you doin' here?
- I want in the competition.
Approach.
Dennis, I told you.
You don't have the right stuff.
I got the right stuff, Frank.
I can win this thing.
I know it!
All right.
Judges' sidebar.
Do you wanna let him in?
Bro, he's been talking about
this modeling thing for years.
If only to shut him up.
Hmm.
- You're in.
- Oh, yeah! Yes! Huh?
[ Shouts, Laughs ]
[ Growls, Mutters,
Laughs ]
Okay. The first competition
is the underwear competition.
Boom!
- How's your face, Dee?
- How do you think
it is, Charlie?
You kept hitting me over
and over in the same spot
with a volleyball.
And I was explicitly clear--
no more Greenman.
Come on!
Greenman's
what makes this thing work.
Greenman is not
what makes it work, Charlie.
My characters
are what make it work.
No more Greenman.
We're not doing it anymore.
All right. Geez, relax.
You're nothing
without Greenman.
Oh, shit.
Dee, you know what?
This is-- This is all,
like, a bad frame and stuff.
This isn't gonna work.
We gotta do it again.
What?
I meant the camera was too low.
We gotta--
[ Clears Throat ]
Hey, diary. It's me.
It's Thursday, September 30,
about midnight.
Uh, I'm alone,
of course, again,
and I just had
a little bit too much ice cream.
Interesting.
Hey, Frank. Can I talk
to you for a second?
What's up?
Bro, originally my plan
was to just bang
a bunch of models, right?
Oh, yeah.
Okay. But after talking
to a few of them,
I feel like I could find
my true love here.
You think you could fall in love
with one of these broads?
Yeah, dude!
Look, eventually
I gotta settle down, right?
Spread my seed.
Haven't you ever seen
The Bachelor? Look, you get
a whole bunch of them together,
you make them compete over you--
bing, bang, boom, soul mate.
Woo-hoo.
That sounds good.
[ Chuckles ]
Okay. You take
the girls--
Uh-huh.
and I'll take Dennis
and the dudes.
Really?
Yeah!
You'll just give me
the girls?
Absolutely.
I can have
my own competition.
Awesome.
Frank, I don't understand it,
but I don't care.
All right. Thanks, bud.
All right.
See ya.
Whatever.
Thank you.
Okay.
All right.
Where are all my male models?
Come forward. Come forward.
Okay. As you know,
in the world of modeling,
you're sometimes asked
to model a theme.
Today's theme is "barnyard."
Okay. Everybody come on
the stage that I have prepared
to give you a little ambience.
Okay. Here is a baby pool
that you are all gonna get into.
And, uh, there's a lot of hay,
and there's
some chickens and ducks.
What the hell, bro?
Is that supposed to be dirt?
It smells like shit.
It is shit.
This is a barnyard.
No one is going to
step in shit, all right?
Uh-- Rex, are you kidding me?
Seriously? You're just gonna
step right in it?
I wanna win, bro.
Billboard.
Dee, what is this getup?
What are you doing now?
What is that?
[ Chinese Accent ]
Oh, okay.
This is Taiwan Tammy.
She on runway
and do a drag queen and nails.
Oh, thank you.
Are you kidding me?
That is extremely racist!
Isn't it awesome?
I'm so excited about this one.
All right. Well,
good luck to you on that.
Why are your hands
in your pockets?
They're itchy.
Your hands are itchy?
My hands are a little itchy.
Your hands are in your pockets
'cause they're itchy?
Goddamn it! I knew it!
Charlie, what are you doing?
I said no Greenman!
Greenman sells
this whole thing!
It doesn't make any sense!
Goddamn it, Charlie!
Hey. I know you.
What?
Yeah. You that, uh--
that girl.
Uh, PatheticGirl43.
PatheticGirl?
I almost didn't
recognize you in that getup.
- But I'd recognize
that whiny voice anywhere.
- Yeah!
Hey, you mind if
we get a picture together?
Yeah, let's get a picture!
I mean, my friends--
I can't believe
you recognized us!
They ain't gonna believe this.
You saw
the YouTube thing, right?
Charlie, what is going on?
I'll show you later.
[ Sighs ]
In other news,
it seems like I have a rash...
in a place where
a sexually active person
should have a rash.
Greenman!
[ Cartoon Sound Effects ]
Oh, my God!
You put that on YouTube?
Oh, my God. I totally did.
Charlie, why would you
do that to me?
Because that's great stuff.
That is
my private video diary!
80,000 hits.
80,000?
80,000 hits, Dee.
That's huge!
That's a big number.
Yeah. Come on.
Don't take this to heart.
[ Exhales ]
Don't take this
the wrong way.
Hey, look. You got recognized
on the street today.
That happened.
So did I.
Well, it was me first.
The point is that's
the first step
to becoming hugely famous--
- Pretty awesome.
- is people noticing you
on the Internet.
80,000 hits.
That's a lot of hits, Charlie.
You know what it's like
for Chocolate Rain when
he goes around in the world?
He gets free food.
He gets free everything,
'cause people love that guy.
Charlie, fire up
that video camera.
There you go.
Okay, Anya. So they are,
in fact, double D's.
That's great news.
[ Chuckles ]
Well, you got a great look--
no denying that.
Let me ask you
a question, though.
Why should I pick you
over the other girls?
I'm willing to do anything
in order to win.
- You're talking about
banging me, right?
- Maybe.
- [ Clicks Tongue ]
Well, if you say yes--
- Yes.
Okay, great.
You said yes.
Okay. Anya said yes.
That's written down now.
Yes.
That's like a contract.
All right. Perfect.
You can't go back on it.
All right. Well,
thank you for coming in.
Thank you.
Nice talking to you.
You too.
You got a great shot.
You got a great ass.
All right.
Wow.
[ Door Opens ]
- Hi.
- Hi! Rachelle!
Yes.
Rachelle,
Rachelle, Rachelle.
Thank you for coming in.
I'm having all the girls come in
just to make sure we vibe.
- Of course.
- What's the difference between
you and the rest of the girls?
Well, my heart
is in this 100%,
and for more
than just a billboard.
For more than a billboard?
That's interesting.
- I haven't heard that yet.
- No?
I feel like there's vibing
happening right now.
- This is the vibing
I'm talking about.
- Yeah.
- I feel like we're
completing each other's--
- Sentences.
Yeah!
I was gonna say "sentences"!
[ Laughs ]
I know.
Oh, my God.
- How did you read my--
- Mind.
I was gonna say "head."
Oh.
But that's okay.
That's all right.
We got--
We're one for two.
Okay.
That's okay.
Fifty percent.
- You and I are gonna
get along very well.
- [ Laughs ]
Rex, that is a sexy jaguar.
I mean,
that jaguar is fierce!
I've-I've-- I've never
been turned on
by a jaguar before.
This has totally changed
my mind toward jaguars.
Dennis, your mule is shit.
I am no longer
turned on by mules.
You gave Rex "jaguar"!
There aren't jaguars in barns!
Plus, what the hell am I
supposed to do with a mule?
You can't make a mule sexy.
Dennis, you've been out-modeled.
I have not been out-modeled.
I haven't even
begun to work this hot body.
What's the next event?
The clothes-off pose-off.
♪♪ [ Disco ]
Oh!
Jesus Christ, Frank!
That burns! What--
What are you doing?
Anything can happen
on a runway, Dennis.
Nobody's gonna throw detergent
in my eyeballs
on a runway, Frank!
And you think that was bad,
check out this tasty delight.
You gotta eat cockroaches next.
You know, man, screw this.
I'm outta here.
Finished.
Jesus, Rex.
I didn't tell you
to start eating yet.
That doesn't disqualify me,
does it?
- No, you're good.
- [ Sighs ]
Oh, hey, diary. Listen.
Today was the worst day ever.
I had an audition
and I didn't get the part,
which is really,
really strange for me.
But then
the casting director called
and they were, like,
"We thought
you were just better
for a different part."
And I was, like,
"That makes more sense."
Cut, cut!
What are you doing?
That was great.
Why don't you do it like
you did the first time?
- This is just weird.
- This is what I do. I talk
into the camera about my life.
You never do this. You have
all these colors on your face.
Your mouth is going like this--
Don't bust my balls.
This is great exposure for me.
This is stupid.
[ Door Closes ]
Hey, Charlie.
You are here! Dee!
What the hell's going on?
She looks like a clown.
I don't know.
Get outta here!
Like a porn star
or something.
He almost didn't
recognize you!
You guys shooting a porn?
- No, we're not--
- Never mind. I don't care.
Listen, we need to get that
company credit card from Frank.
Yeah? What's up?
Man, dude,
I realized something.
I don't need validation anymore.
How great is that?
But what I do need is
the company credit card...
so that I can
buy myself a billboard,
get myself out there...
and show the entire world
that Dennis Reynolds...
still has a rocking body
that deserves to be worshipped.
Get out of here!
We're in the middle
of something!
- No, you get out of here!
- This is my place!
I need that billboard!
Hang on a second.
Okay, look. Guys, guys.
[ Sighs ]
There's a way to make you guys
both happy, all right?
I got a pretty good plan
how to do this.
Hey, everybody.
PatheticGirl43 here,
coming to you live...
with Philadelphia's
next top model, Dennis Reynolds.
Dennis, tell us what it's like
to be so handsome.
Well, I like to think I've been
this handsome since birth,
possibly even earlier--
Oh!
Greenman!
[ Gasping ]
This shamrock will be awarded
to the winner...
as a symbol of my vote
and love for this competition.
Rachelle, you taught me
about love,
respect, inner beauty.
Dominique, you banged me,
like, right away.
[ Chuckles ]
I hardly had to do anything.
Tabitha, you did the same.
But most importantly,
you banged each other.
And you let me watch.
Awesome.
[ Inhales ]
[ Sighs ]
But when I was making
this decision,
I thought long and hard,
and I thought,
"I have to go with my heart."
So I'm gonna do something
a little unorthodox here.
[ Sighs ]
A top o' the morning...
to both of you!
- [ Both Screaming ]
- [ Rachelle ]
What?
I had two of them!
I had another one here.
I tricked you.
I got both of you guys.
But you just said
that I taught you
about inner beauty and respect.
Yeah, but this whole thing's
about banging,
and you didn't bang me. So--
You're a dick!
I know!
And that's what I learned.
[ Chuckles ]
Hey-o! Check it out.
Check it out!
What is it?
I'll tell you
what it is, bitch.
[ Door Closes ]
It's a YouTube video that me,
Dee and Charlie just made.
It's gonna get a million hits.
So guess what, pal?
Don't need your billboard.
I'm going viral.
I'm glad you don't need it,
because you can't have it
because it's already up.
What?
Yeah. I put it up right
after you called me ugly.
There's no billboard?
Oh, yeah.
Sorry about that, Rex.
My bad.
So, wait. If you already
put the billboard up,
wh-what did you put on it?
♪♪ [ Disco ]
[ Synthesized Voice ]
♪ A.R.S. ♪
♪♪ [ Ends ]
[ Voices Speaking Backwards ]